Nitesh Kumar

Senior Web Designer

Address: Jaipur

Email: niteshmeena4451@gmail.com

Mobile: +91-9694284451

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nitesh-meena-706838223/

Career Objective:

Seeking a full-time, challenging career in a suitable environment, to build a career in a progressive organization that will provide me exciting opportunities to learn more and utilize my skills. Overall, 7+ years of IT industry Knowledge. Have worked on many various projects and made them successful.

Personal Details:

Date of Birth - 08th September 1989

Gender – Male Marital Status – Married Nationality – India

Education Details

Degree	Year of Passing	Board /university
B.Com	2010-2011	Rajasthan University, Rajasthan
HSC	2007	Rajasthan Board
SSC	2005	Rajasthan Board

Technical Skills:

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Bootstrap 4,5
- SCSS
- jQuery
- WordPress
- Abode Photoshop
- Adobe Dreamweaver
- Visual Studio Code
- Sublime
- I have a basic knowledge of React.js
- I have a basic knowledge of Git

Experiences:

StriveMindz (2021 - Present)

3 Years of experience in StriveMindz as part of Web-Designer, I have been involved in the creation of multiple project-related Logo Designing, PSD, UI, UX.

BVM Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd (2017-2021)

- 4.10 Years of experience as part of Web-Designer, I have beeninvolved in the creation of Multiple Website Projects.
- Experienced in Custom designing.

Internship:

Organization Name: DAACDesignation: Web Designer

• Duration: 8 Months

Projects: (websites worked on):

- https://www.quizwithairindia.com/
- https://www.oakfield-dc.com/
- https://bristoltaxihire.co.uk/
- https://vsualthree60.com
- https://spectrumjewel.com/
- https://www.helimods.com/
- https://sprachjet.com/
- https://www.melbourneheart.com.au/
- https://www.mooloolababeachpharmacy.com.au/
- https://noosahillresort.com.au/
- https://www.cafeforsale.com.au/

Hobbies:

- Traveling
- Gaming

Personal Traits:

- Excellent grasping capability and understanding of the concepts.
- Ability to adjust according to the situation.
- A Self-motivated team player, with excellent confidence & commitment

Declaration:

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

(Nitesh Kumar)